mytoday.com 2011-10-07

# Privacy Policy | mytoday - SMS subscriptions and SMS alerts on World Cup, IPL and 250+ exciting topics including News, Cricket, Bollywood, Astrology, Love and more.

Netcore Solutions Pvt. Ltd. owns http://mytoday.com (“ **Site** “) and Netcore Solutions Pvt. Ltd. including its subsidiaries and affiliates respect your privacy. This Privacy Policy provides succinctly the manner in which your data is collected and used by http://mytoday.com. 

You are advised to please read the Privacy Policy carefully. By submitting information to us, either by visiting or using the Site and/or by registering for, accessing and/or using the Service, you are accepting the terms of this Privacy Policy and those included in our [Terms of Service](http://blog.mytoday.com/tos). You agree to the collection and use of your data by us in the manner provided in this Privacy Policy. 

WE WANT YOU TO

  * Feel comfortable using our Site;
  * Feel secure submitting information to us;
  * Contact us with your questions or concerns about privacy on this Site; and
  * Know that by using our Site, you are consenting to the collection of certain data.

WHAT INFORMATION IS, OR MAY BE, COLLECTED FROM YOU?

If you access our Site through your computers, we will automatically receive and collect certain anonymous information in standard usage logs through our Web server, including 

  * Computer-identification information obtained from “cookies,” sent to your browser from a web server cookie stored on your hard drive;
  * An IP address, assigned to the computer which you use;
  * The domain server through which you access our service;
  * The type of computer you are using; and
  * The type of web browser you are using;

We may collect from time to time the following personally identifiable information about you:

  * Name including first and last name
  * Alternate email address
  * Mobile phone number and contact details
  * ZIP/Postal code
  * Demographic profile (like your age, gender, occupation, education, address and durables owned);
  * Preferences and interests (such as news, sports, travel and so on);
  * Financial information (like account or credit card numbers);
  * Opinions of features on our websites; and
  * Lifestyle information and any other information collected in relation to your use of our products and services.

We may also collect the following information:

  * About the Products and Services you access.
  * The links you click on our site.
  * The number of times you access the page.

You can terminate your account in accordance to the Terms of Service set out on [http://mytoday.com](http://mytoday.com/). However, your information may remain stored in archive on our servers even after the deletion or the termination of your account. 

**WHO COLLECTS THE INFORMATION?**

We will collect anonymous traffic information from you when you visit [http://mytoday.com](http://mytoday.com/). We will collect personally identifiable information about you only as part of a voluntary registration process, on-line survey, or contest or any combination thereof. 

The Site contains links to other Web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such Web sites which we do not own, manage or control. We make chat rooms, forums, instant messenger and message boards and other services available to you. Please understand that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. We have no control over its use and you should exercise caution when disclosing your personal information to anyone. 

**HOW IS THE INFORMATION USED?**

We use your personal information for:

  * Processing your orders or applications;
  * Carrying out credit checking and scoring (unless we have agreed otherwise);
  * Providing you with products and/or services requested (including the presentation or elimination of calling or connected line identification) or administering your account;
  * Settling accounts with those who provide related services to us;
  * Dealing with requests, enquiries or complaints and other customer care related activities; and all other general administrative and business purposes;
  * Help us provide personalized features;
  * Tailor our Site to your interest;
  * To get in touch with you when necessary;
  * Inclusion in any telephone or similar directory or directory enquiry service provided or operated by us or by a third party (subject to any objection or preference you may have indicated to us in writing);
  * Carrying out any activity in connection with a legal, governmental or regulatory requirement on us or in connection with legal proceedings, crime or fraud prevention, detection or prosecution; and
  * To preserve social history as governed by existing law or policy.

We use contact information internally to:   
Carrying out market and product analysis and marketing our and our group companies products and services generally; 

  * Contact you as a survey respondent;
  * Notify you if you win any contest; and
  * Send you promotional materials from our contest sponsors or advertisers.

Generally, we use anonymous traffic information to:

  * Remind us of who you are in order to deliver to you a better and more personalized service from both an advertising and an editorial perspective;
  * Recognize your access privileges to our Site;
  * Track your entries in some of our promotions, sweepstakes and contests to indicate a player’s progress through the promotion and to track entries, submissions, and status in prize drawings;
  * Make sure that you don’t see the same ad repeatedly;
  * Help diagnose problems with our server;
  * Administer our Site; and
  * Track your session so that we can understand better how people use our Site.

**WITH WHOM WILL YOUR INFORMATION BE SHARED?**

We may share your personal information to third parties. If we do this, we will only disclose your information to:

  * Our group companies, consultants, authors, publishers, partners, agents who may in India use and disclose your information for the same purposes as us;
  * Credit reference agencies (unless we have agreed otherwise) who may share your information with other organisations and who may keep a record of the searches we make against your name;
  * Those providing telephone and similar directories or directory enquiry services
  * Advertisers on an aggregate basis only
  * Anyone we transfer our business to in respect of which you are a customer or a potential customer;
  * Anyone who assists us in protecting the operation of our networks and systems, including the use of monitoring and detection in order to identify potential threats, such as hacking and virus dissemination and other security vulnerabilities;
  * To help investigate, prevent or take action regarding unlawful and illegal activities, suspected fraud, potential threat to the safety or security of any person, violations of mytoday.com’s terms of use or to defend against legal claims;
  * Special circumstances such as compliance with subpoenas, court orders, requests/order from legal authorities or law enforcement agencies requiring such disclosure.

If you have opted in to receiving marketing material from us, we may also provide your personal information to carefully selected third parties who we reasonably believe provide products or services that may be of interest to you and who have contracted with us to keep the information confidential, or who are subject to obligations to protect your personal information. 

If you would like to opt-out of receiving our marketing materials, please email to help@mytoday.com. Please note that we will still need to send you essential information about your account or changes to your service. 

**WHAT CHOICES ARE AVAILABLE TO YOU REGARDING COLLECTION, USE AND DISTRIBUTION OF YOUR INFORMATION?**

You may change your interests at any time and may opt-in or opt-out of any marketing / promotional / newsletters mailings. We reserve the right to send you certain service related communication, considered to be a part of your account without offering you the facility to opt-out. You may update your information and change your account settings at any time. 

Upon request, we will remove/block your personally identifiable information from our database, thereby canceling your registration. See Contact information below. However, your information may remain stored in archive on our servers even after the deletion or the termination of your account. 

If we plan to use your personally identifiable information for any commercial purposes, we will notify you at the time we collect that information and allow you to opt-out of having your information used for those purposes. 

You can accept or decline the cookies. All sites that are customizable require that you accept cookies. You also must accept cookies to register as someone for access to some of our services. 

**WHAT SECURITY PROCEDURES ARE IN PLACE TO PROTECT INFORMATION FROM LOSS, MISUSE OR ALTERATION?**

To protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control, we have in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures. For example, our servers are accessible only to authorized personnel and that your information is shared with respective personnel on need to know basis to complete the transaction and to provide the services requested by you. 

Although we will endeavor to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information, transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. By using this Site, you agree that we will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties. 

**HOW CAN YOU CORRECT INACCURACIES IN THE INFORMATION?**

To correct or update any information you have provided, our Site allows you to do it online. In the event of loss of access details you can use any of the following options:

  * Send an e-mail to help@mytoday.com

**POLICY UPDATES**

We reserve the right to change or update this policy at any time by placing a prominent notice on our site. Such changes shall be effective immediately upon posting to this site. 

You are can offer your views, suggestions, comments, if any, by submitting the filled in form at [http://blog.mytoday.com/contact/](http://blog.mytoday.com/contact-us/) online. 

**CONTACT INFORMATION**   
You can contact us at: 

Netcore Solutions Pvt. Ltd.  
402, Peninsula Chambers, Ganpat Rao Kadam Marg, Lower Parel (West), Mumbai 400 013. India. 

Top
